<resources>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="email">Email Id</string>
    <string name="passowrd">Password</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="show_pwd">Show Password</string>
    <string name="hide_pwd">Hide Password</string>
    <string name="forgot">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="closebutton">Close Button for Activity</string>
    <string name="newUser">Not a Member yet? Sign Up here.</string>
    <string name="fullName">Full Name</string>
    <string name="mobileNumber">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="confirmPassword">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">By clicking SignUp you agree all the Terms and Conditions.</string>
    <string name="signUp">SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="already_user">Already have Account? Login here.</string>
    <string name="registered_emailid">Please enter your Registered Email Id below:</string>
    <string name="submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="back">BACK</string>
    <string name="app_name">Starbucks App</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Starbucks was founded by Jerry Baldwin, Gordon Bowker, and Zev Siegel, opening its first store in 1971 across the street from the historic Pike Place Market in Seattle. The three Starbucks founders had two things in common; they were all coming from academia, and they all loved coffee and tea. They invested and borrowed some money to open the first store in Seattle and named it “Starbucks” after the first mate in Herman Melville’s classic novel Moby Dick.

Alfred Peet, a coffee-roasting entrepreneur, was a major inspiration to the founders of Starbucks. Peet was a Dutch immigrant who had begun importing fine arabica coffees into the United States during the 1950s. In 1966 he opened a small store, Peet’s Coffee and Tea, in Berkeley, California, that specialized in importing first-rate coffees and teas. Peet’s success encouraged the Starbucks founders to base their business model on selling high-quality coffee beans and equipment, and Peet’s became the initial supplier of green coffee beans to Starbucks. The partners then purchased a used roaster from Holland, and Baldwin and Bowker experimented with Alfred Peet’s roasting techniques to create their own blends and flavours.

By the early 1980s, Starbucks had opened four stores in Seattle that stood out from the competitors with their top-quality fresh-roasted coffees. In 1980 Siegel decided to pursue other interests and left the two remaining partners, with Baldwin assuming the role of company president.


"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
